{
    "subject": "resource/Trevor_Thompson_(footballer,_born_1936)",
    "predicate": "ontology/team",
    "object": "resource/Derry_City_F.C.",
    "human_readable": "Trevor Thompson (footballer, born 1936) played for Derry City F.C.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9186868667602539,
            "question": "Was Trevor Thompson a footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8628999590873718,
            "question": "Is Trevor Thompson known for playing football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.826632022857666,
            "question": "For which football club did Trevor Thompson play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8119956851005554,
            "question": "What year was Trevor Thompson born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8094069957733154,
            "question": "Who is Trevor Thompson?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.761936366558075,
            "question": "In what year did Trevor Thompson start playing football?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7566688656806946,
            "question": "What position did Trevor Thompson play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7286445498466492,
            "question": "What sport did Trevor Thompson play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6931912302970886,
            "question": "What is the name of the club Trevor Thompson played for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5449373126029968,
            "question": "Can you tell me about Trevor Thompson's career?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Trevor Thompson (footballer, born 1936) played for Derry City F.C.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3670_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the club Trevor Thompson played for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3670_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport did Trevor Thompson play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3670_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What position did Trevor Thompson play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3670_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3670_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the context information provided, here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that according to the documents, Trevor Thompson played in the Irish League as a centre forward, most famously with Glentoran in the 1960s (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3670/re-ranker-msmarco/21.txt), but there is no mention of him playing for Derry City F.C."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do not mention Trevor Thompson playing for Derry City F.C. They only state that he was a Northern Irish footballer who played in the Irish League, most famously with Glentoran in the 1960s."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided that suggests Trevor Thompson (footballer, born 1936) played for Derry City F.C.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "gemma2": {
            "reason": "There is no mention of Derry City F.C. in any of the provided text descriptions of Trevor Thompson's football career.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "There is no information anywhere in the provided context about Trevor Thompson playing for Derry City F.C.",
            "category": 1
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "The context information mentions Trevor Thompson played for Glentoran and Lincoln City, but does not mention Derry City F.C.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}